{"quiz":{"id":"M0MASI","time_zone":-7,"scoring":"Scored","max_score":5,"questions":{"Q1244761":{"question":"How long have you been self employed? ","type":"Select One","max_score":0,"answers":[{"answer":"Under a year","score":0},{"answer":"1-2 years","score":0},{"answer":"3-5 years","score":0},{"answer":"Over 5 years","score":0}]},"Q1244762":{"question":"What type of business structure do you have?","type":"Select One","max_score":2,"answers":[{"answer":"Sole Proprietor","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":0,"score":1}]},{"answer":"Single Member LLC","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":1,"score":1},{"id":0,"score":1}]},{"answer":"C corp","score":2},{"answer":"S corp","score":2},{"answer":"Partnership","score":2},{"answer":"Other\/ I am not sure","score":1}]},"Q1244763":{"question":"There are benefits and disadvantages to each type of business structure. Do you feel that you understand which type would benefit you most?","type":"Select One","max_score":0,"answers":[{"answer":"I think so but am not sure","score":0},{"answer":"Yes","score":0},{"answer":"I don't think so","score":0},{"answer":"No, I'd like someone to review my situation and help me decide","score":0}]},"Q1244764":{"question":"Is your business profitable? ","type":"Select One","max_score":0,"answers":[{"answer":"Yes","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":0,"score":1}]},{"answer":"No","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":1,"score":1}]}]},"Q1244765":{"question":"Do you have any employees?  ","type":"Select One","max_score":0,"answers":[{"answer":"None","score":0},{"answer":"1-3","score":0},{"answer":"4-8","score":0},{"answer":"9+","score":0}]},"Q1244766":{"question":"What is your marital status?","type":"Select One","max_score":1,"answers":[{"answer":"Married or civil union","score":1,"outcomes":[{"id":0,"score":1}]},{"answer":"Engaged","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":1,"score":1}]},{"answer":"Single","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":1,"score":1}]},{"answer":"It's complicated...","score":0}]},"Q1244767":{"question":"Depending on your business structure, sometimes having your spouse work as an employee is required, other times it isn't. Does your spouse currently help with the business?","type":"Select One","max_score":1,"answers":[{"answer":"Yes, they are a paid employee","score":1,"outcomes":[{"id":0,"score":1}]},{"answer":"Yes, but they are unpaid","score":1,"outcomes":[{"id":0,"score":1}]},{"answer":"No, they are not involved","score":0,"outcomes":[{"id":2,"score":1}]},{"answer":"Not married","score":0}]},"Q1244768":{"question":"If your spouse could help, even minimally, it could help qualify you. (Tasks could include simple things such as: filing, answering phone calls, responding to email, bookkeeping, etc) Would this be a possibility for you?","type":"Select One","max_score":1,"answers":[{"answer":"Yes","score":1},null,null,{"answer":"No","score":0}]},"Q1244769":{"question":"Have you ever heard of an HRA and do you know how they work?","type":"Select One","max_score":0,"answers":[{"answer":"No","score":0},{"answer":"No, but I'd like to learn more about how they work","score":0},{"answer":"Yes, I've heard about them but don't know much about them","score":0},{"answer":"Yes, I've heard about them and have considered setting one up","score":0}]},"Q1244759":{"question":"First Name:","type":"Text","lead_capture":true},"Q1244760":{"question":"Email:","type":"Text","format":"Email","lead_capture":true}},"pages":9,"grades":[null,null,null,null,null,null,null,{"name":"Hooray!  Chances look pretty good!","description":"<div>It looks like you could qualify. To see your full results and find out how to claim your refund click here: <a href=\"https:\/\/taxbot.leadpages.co\/hra-2017-quiz-likely-qualified\/\">https:\/\/taxbot.leadpages.co\/hra-2017-quiz-likely-qualified\/<\/a><\/div>","maximum_score":0,"range":{"min":2,"max":10,"type":"score"}},{"name":" It looks like you may not qualify for an HRA at this time","description":"<div>To see your full results and find out what you might be able to do to qualify, click here: <a href=\"https:\/\/taxbot.leadpages.co\/hra-2017-quiz-unqualified\/\">https:\/\/taxbot.leadpages.co\/hra-2017-quiz-unqualified\/<\/a><\/div>","maximum_score":0,"range":{"min":0,"max":1,"type":"score"}}]},"responses":[{"id":3182057,"geo":{"country":"United States","city":"Ogden","region":"Utah","lat":41.2229995727539,"lng":-111.973999023438},"ip":["50.252.139.130"],"browser":"Mozilla\/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_12_3) AppleWebKit\/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome\/56.0.2924.87 Safari\/537.36","device_id":"855411456-130-4166994125","times":{"start":1489700977240,"end":1489700979740,"pages":[1176,392,3,3,482,444]},"score":2,"percent":40,"questions":{"Q1244761":{"text":"Under a year","score":0,"answers":[0]},"Q1244762":{"text":"C corp","score":2,"answers":[2]},"Q1244763":{"text":"","score":0,"answers":[]},"Q1244764":{"text":"","score":0,"answers":[]},"Q1244765":{"text":"1-3","score":0,"answers":[1]},"Q1244766":{"text":"It's complicated...","score":0,"answers":[3]},"Q1244767":{"text":"","score":0,"answers":[-1]},"Q1244768":{"text":"","score":0,"answers":[-1]},"Q1244769":{"text":"","score":0,"answers":[-1]},"Q1244759":{"score":0,"text":"Bazinga"},"Q1244760":{"score":0,"text":"caseym@taxbot.com"}},"grade":{"number":8,"name":"Hooray!  Chances look pretty good!","description":"<div>It looks like you could qualify. To see your full results and find out how to claim your refund click here: <a href=\"https:\/\/taxbot.leadpages.co\/hra-2017-quiz-likely-qualified\/\">https:\/\/taxbot.leadpages.co\/hra-2017-quiz-likely-qualified\/<\/a><\/div>"},"contact":{"emails":["caseym@taxbot.com"]}}]}